<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fixed on Mehdi Azarmi</title>
    <link>https://mazarmi.github.io/fixed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fixed on Mehdi Azarmi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 16:35:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mazarmi.github.io/fixed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>publication</title>
      <link>https://mazarmi.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 16:35:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mazarmi.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>Please refer to Google Scholar for the latest udpates.
 End to End Security in Service Oriented Architecture. M. Azarmi, P. Angin, B. Bhargava, N. Ahmed , A. Sinclair, et al. 31st International Symposium on Reliable Distributed Systems (IEEE SRDS 2012), 2012, Under Submission. Novel Secure and Dynamic Clustering Protocols in Wireless Sensor Networks. R. Jiang, M. Azarmi, T. Gong, B. Bhargava. Elsevier Computers &amp;amp; Security, 2011, Under Review. Minimizing Collaborative Attacks in a Real Heterogeneous Mobile Ad Hoc Network Using Cooperative Immunization Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mazarmi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 06:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mazarmi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I received my Ph.D. in Computer Science from Purdue University. I was affiliated with the Center for Education and Research in Information Assurance and Security (CERIAS).
I&amp;rsquo;m currently interested in designing reliable and massively scalable distributed systems. Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on multiple areas of information security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://mazarmi.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 00:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mazarmi.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>  rook (An Open, Cloud Native, and Universal Distributed Storage): Implemented the etcd manager to elastically expand and shrink the etcd cluster based on the cluster&amp;rsquo;s status. discovery service: Improved and expanded the etcd discovery service to reflect the latest cluster membership. distcron: A Distributed Cron.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>